togoparts.com 2019-09-06

# Privacy | Online Bike Shop | Togoparts

Because your privacy is important to us, togoparts.com operates by the following principles: 

## Principle 1.

Togoparts.com collects information during the registration process to operate the site ("Registration Information"). togoparts.com explicitly asks when it needs information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information"). The Personal Information togoparts.com collects includes first and last name. In addition to Personal Information collected, togoparts.com also collects non-personally identifiable information (often referred to as demographic information) such as: country, city and email address. You may update your Registration Information at any time from within your togoparts.com account after you have logged in. 

## Principle 2.

Your Registration Information (brief profile) is necessary for your membership at togoparts and used only for demographic statistics . Your non-personally identifiable information from your togoparts.com (such as email address, icq, webpage URLs) may be shared within the website. None of your other Registration Information is shared with third parties. The Detailed Profile can be optionally be entered and is intended for sharing within the website. the privacy policy does not cover information revealed from the detailed profile.

## Principle 3.

Togoparts.com will not send you any unsolicited information, including e-mail, except as mentioned below. togoparts.com may also send periodic member letters to announce important service changes, new features, updates and news about other products and services. togoparts.com will not send you unsolicited e-mail regarding any third party commercial offers or advertisements. 

## Principle 4.

If at any time you believe that togoparts.com has not adhered to these principles, please notify us by e-mail at feedback@togoparts.com. If you have questions about this policy, please e-mail us at feedback@togoparts.com

## What about Cookies?

Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can make the Web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many major Web sites use them to provide useful features for their customers. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of a Web site if you do so. 

## What about the registration information?

Togoparts.com site's registation form requires you to give us contact information (like your name and email address) and unique identifiers (like a password). Unique identifiers (such as passwords) are collected to verify your identity in our system. By registering, users can take advantage of personalization (the ability to select content according to a user-supplied profile) as well as to gain access to other parts of the website like the Forums. This is information which does not personally identify you, but which may be helpful for improving the community services. Generally, this information is collected through "traffic data" and may entail the use of "Cookies" "IP addresses" or other numeric codes used to identify a computer.

We partner with Facebook to simplify account registration and login. It is not different from a normal account registration. As our policy above, we respect your privacy and we do not share any of your personal data with 3rd party.

## How do I correct or change Registration Information that I have given to togoparts.com?

You may update this information at any time after you have logged in. Links will will appear in the login status box usually located on the top left corner of the page.

## Is my Registration Information secure from others using the togoparts.com site?

Registration Information collected by togoparts.com is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public. 

##   
How else might someone learn of my Personal Information while visiting another site?

In addition to directly providing information to togoparts.com, you might also provide Personal Information through e-mail exchanges, message boards, forums, marketplace or bulletin board use made available to you on other sites. Chat sessions and bulletin board or newsgroup use is considered public and you are responsible for your actions in these areas. The togoparts.com Privacy Statement does not cover this type of transfer of your Personal Information. You should always be careful when distributing your Personal Information in this manner. 

## What about links to Other Sites?

As a regulary updated News front site, togoparts.com contains links to other sites. togoparts.com does not control the information collection of sites that can be reached through links from togoparts. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data or solicit personal information. If you have questions about the data collection practices of linked sites, please contact those websites directly.

## What about Surveys?

Occasionally togoparts.com conducts polls and user surveys to better target our content to our audience. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with advertisers and partners. We will never share any of this information about specific individuals with any third party.

## Your consent and changes to the Private Policy

By using togoparts.com and the rest of the togoparts.com services, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this policy. togoparts.com may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time.

Updated: Jan 2016
